Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth.
People tell me my head's in the clouds.
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreaming of you.
You are the treasure I found.
So bright, so bold, it's so elusive.
It's hard to look away.
Even though it's blinding me.
There are no words to
describe how I feel inside.
I'm really, really stuck on you.
I have to follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
And I won't stop till I
get there, you will see.
You're all I need to have
the strength to believe.
Believe in wonder.
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
I'm gonna share them
with you, a love so true.
You're all I want,
together we can move on.
We live how we want to.
There is no limit to us.
We have the power of love.
We don't wanna live ordinary life.
We have a chance to live in paradise.
We live in wonderland.
Our nightmares aren't
over, Princess. Not yet.
The man's right!
Yeah!
I wish what happened was a
nightmare, but it was real!
We want justice!
We saw King Cobra attack
Nanohana with our own eyes!
That's right!
And those damn royals shot Koza, too!
You expect us all just to forgive
them after what they did?!
Our nightmares will only be over once
we've killed every royal in this country!
Royal Army, drop your weapons now!
Up there!
Chaka!
Is he serious?
Yes!
Ma! Ma! Ma!
That goes for you too, Rebel Army.
Igaram!
Squad captain!
He made it back.
May we meet again safely in
our homeland, Princess Phoebe.
Hey, it's that cross-dressing
guy from Whiskey Peak.
He's still alive.
Hey, who is that guy?
Boy, can you talk to me?
That's the boy from Nanohana.
The kid who was harmed by
those royal army goons.
No, that's not true!
It wasn't them!
The people who did this looked
like members of the royal army,
but it really wasn't them!
Everyone, please listen!
This is what I saw!
Ooh!
It feels so good to get back into gear!
That's right.
We were all manipulated.
This battle was a plot from the beginning.
Yakuza, leader...
Royal or rebel, I'll
explain it to you all.
Everything that has
befallen our fair country.
But only if you drop your weapons.
Princess?
My friends, where are they?
Come on, Usopp, I know
you're hurt, but keep up.
I wish I could, but I'm coming down with,
if I walk anymore, I'll die disease.
I'll drag you then. Wait,
let me go, or I can come down with, if
I get dragged anymore, I'll die disease.
Found him.
Who are you uh just
travelers passing through
the guy on your back's one of us as well!
We'll take him now thanks old man!
Hold on if you're with this
young man then you must
be those Pirates who brought
Vivi back to this country?
Wait how would you know all
that daddy everyone? Everyone!
Hey, Phoebe!
Daddy?
What?!
This guy is Phoebe's dad?!
Guess that makes you the king.
Yes,
and I'd be a dead king if it weren't for
the efforts of your
brave young friend here.
Even though he'd come into contact
with Crocodile's poison hook,
I still managed to carry
myself and another to safety.
An unbelievable strength he has.
Should we be worried about the poison?
I mean, is he going to be all right?
It's okay.
It should be neutralized by now.
However, his injuries need to be treated.
So do yours as well.
We'll wait.
You need to be somewhere else.
Go back to the square, Vivi.
He's right.
Now that the war's over,
it's only fitting for the king and princess
to say a few words, don't you think?
You know, tell them what really happened.
Right, and I can tell them
all about you guys, too.
Vivi, dear, please don't.
We're a band of notorious pirates.
The last thing we need are
our faces and names known.
But what we do need is food.
And rest.
We'd like to crash at the
palace, if that's okay.
Yes, sir.
Understood, Captain Smoker.
Are you serious?
Crocodile?
He was the one behind all this?
All this time, we thought he was a hero.
Over there! Look!
It's the Marines!
I've just been informed that a
Baroque Works ship has been seized,
one that makes artificial
rain using dance powder.
You being Baroque Works president,
I've been ordered to tell you this.
Sir Crocodile, one of the
Seven Warlords of the Sea.
Tell me!
Tell me which way Crocodile went!
By the authority of the world government,
I hereby strip you of your
authorization to capture enemy ships,
as well as all the titles and rights
bestowed upon you by the government.
Additionally, you and all Baroque
Works agents are under arrest.
Oh, that's my cue to leave.
We rebels, we've done horrible
things that could never be undone.
Leader, I don't know what to
say to him, to any of them.
We all feel regret over what has
happened, but that's natural.
King Cobra, your majesty.
We've lost so much and gained nothing.
We've been divided.
But now we have a chance
to take a step forward.
No matter who you fought against,
the battle did occur and it's over.
We must put this strife behind
us and become one again.
The king's right.
Unfortunately, there's nothing
we can do about what's happened.
We cannot change the past.
There's one thing we can change,
however, and that's our future.
He's so wise.
A future where all of
Alabasta is united once more.
The monumental battle that will be
engraved upon the annals of history...
...and even more importantly, the
battle that will never be told...
...is finally over.
Smoker, where the hell
is this rain coming from?
Don't tell me you used the
dance powder on this ship.
Don't be stupid.
Believe it or not, I know
better than to commit a crime.
We haven't seen each
other in quite some time,
and the first thing you do is
blame me for some natural rain.
And I was about to tell you you look good.
You're right.
It was a lousy welcome. Hina's sorry.
As for the compliment,
I can't believe the white hunter
would say something so sweet.
My, you've actually softened up a little.
Shut your trap, Hina.
Is that what I get for helping you out?
And I might add, for
the umpteenth time, too?
My elite unit found this ship for you.
A thanks would be nice.
Upset.
Hina's upset.
Oh, don't give me that speech.
We're all marines. Oh, honestly.
I don't know how poor Tashigi
puts up with you, Smoker.
She manages somehow.
I need you to take this ship into HQ me.
Also Toshiki is going to
be bringing crocodile here
kill two birds with one
stone and take him with you?
Give me a break.
I'm an officer not your
personal errand girl
It's heads.
It's tails you lose, errand girl?
You're a real piece of work.
You know that smoker
I thought a few years of command would
change you, but I guess I was wrong.
Hina's disappointed.
I'm well aware of that.
And I don't care.
Negative.
That's an order.
Sergeant Major!
With all due respect, why not?
With your permission, we can capture
all the Straw Hats in one fell swoop!
Denied!
I will not allow you to
lay a hand on any of them!
Is that understood?
But we're never going to get
another chance like this again.
They're sitting ducks right now.
Hang on, Leader.
We'll get you taken care of.
And your father, too.
Leader, there was a sandstorm in Yuba.
Still a war reward, as always, I see.
I don't know how Yuba fared,
but take my word for it,
a sandstorm is no match
for my stubborn old man.
I hope so.
Don't worry about me either.
I've got his blood in my veins.
As soon as I get treated,
I'll head to Yuba.
I'll keep you updated.
So don't worry, alright?
Alright.
It's actually raining!
This is the first time in three years!
It's a miracle!
This rain will end the rebellion!
Our foolish sons will come home!
How long are you going
to be stubborn, old man?
Father, look around.
Yuba is finished.
A ghost town.
What are you going to do here by yourself?
Are you going to dry up and die too?
Old man!
See, son.
Look there!
The rain has come back.
Just like I told you, I knew
that it would come back.
I was right. Yes.
Right as rain.
The rain that falls in the kingdom
is more than just a physical one,
but also a symbolic one that washes away
the bitter tears of its recent past.
Princess Vivi, what
are you still doing up?
Oh, hey, Couran, it's nothing.
You can't sleep, huh?
It's not that.
I just don't want to sleep right now.
I'd rather watch the rain fall.
It's been so long since I've seen it.
Bebe, about Pell.
He was, without a doubt, the strongest,
most loyal and dignified
warrior I ever served with.
He was.
I just wish I could have said thank you.
He'd be greatly honored by that princess.
Captain Smoker, Ms.
Hina, Sergeant Major Tashigi has arrived.
Welcome back, Sergeant Major!
It sure has been a while, Tashigi.
Nina?
Glad to see you again.
If you'll excuse me.
I'm a little tired, so I'm
going to go get some rest.
We're back, Captain Smoker.
Did you get my report? Sure did.
Thanks for your work.
I heard about what happened
with the Straw Hats.
I'm sorry, sir.
I helped the pirates.
We also had an opportunity to
capture them, and I let it slip away.
It's all my fault.
My actions were shameful. I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing? Stop it.
Didn't you follow your
justice like I told you to?
No, that's not it.
Sergeant Major.
It's just that I didn't
have any other choice.
Justice is only for
the people who take it.
That's the kind of world we live in, girl.
Tell me which way Crocodile went!
Which way did he go?
I was charged with bringing Crocodile
in, but I wasn't strong enough.
When Straw Hat Luffy asked where he
was, all I could do was tell him.
I was also no match for Nico Robin.
I was too weak.
So there was no justice I could follow.
I get it.
You thought you were strong
enough to defeat Crocodile.
But you weren't.
So the Straw Hats stepped
up and did it instead.
The Straw Hats know what you have
to do to survive in this sea.
You either step up or you die.
You did what you could
but it wasn't enough.
Luckily, you're still alive.
Learn from this experience.
With your permission, sir.
I'm going to get some
rest, if you'll excuse me.
Toshiki.
Don't cry about it.
Do what the Straw Hats did.
Step up and become stronger.
Sir, yes, sir!
I just wish the rest of you had the
same kind of guts that she does.
All right, get those prisoners
loaded on this ship. Yes, sir!
Captain HQ for you on the
transponder snail this
is Marine Headquarters
calling could I speak with?
Captain Smoker please
smoker here congratulations
on subduing Sir Crocodile
captain as a result The
top officials of the World
Government have ordered
that both you and Sergeant
Major Tashigi Be given
medals for your efforts
subduing no wait hold on a
minute we aren't the ones
who took Down Crocodile it
was the Straw Hats did
anyone even bother to read
the report furthermore as
Thanks for your gallantry,
it's also been decided that each of
you will be promoted by one rank.
Hey, I told you, for the
umpteenth time, it wasn't us.
Me and Toshiki weren't the ones who
stopped Crocodile and Baroque Works.
It was those damn straw-hat pirates.
Stop, Smoker, it's no use.
It's obvious at this point
that the government's
going to cover up this entire incident.
Think of the scandal if word of
what really happened got out.
Alabasta was almost toppled, and
it wasn't saved by the government,
but by a group of wanted pirates.
And of course,
we expect both of you to
attend the awards ceremony
where your medals will
be - Like hell we will!
Smoker, don't be dumb. Accept it.
If you disobey the brass, you
could get court-martialed.
Well, better that than live a lie.
We didn't take Crocodile down.
My subordinate's in tears
because we couldn't.
Hey, you.
Could you pass on a personal message
from me to the old geezers at HQ?
Don't do it, Smoker!
Tell him I said go to hell.
My!
Your medicine-making skills are
so innovative and practical.
It's amazing.
You're a genius, my boy.
Where in the world did
you learn such techniques?
Tony was a practicing
doctor back in Drum Kingdom.
He was?
You mean the same drum that was once
renowned for its advanced medicine?
No wonder this little
fellow is so talented. Wow!
I've been a doctor for 40 years,
but even I don't know the
techniques and remedies that you do.
You're far younger than I, but
it's obvious I'm no match for you.
You're clearly the superior doctor.
Bravo, my boy! Shut up, jerk!
Stop saying that!
I can't stand it!
Get out of here or you're
gonna talk like that!
He's offering me tea in a
chair despite what he's saying.
Does he want me to stay?
He certainly does.
Well, in that case, show me
more of your incredible talents.
I said shut up.
If only I could have splendid
skills such as yours.
I can't tell you how impressed I am.
Get out of here.
I can't take it anymore.
Hey, does anybody have any more lumber?
No, I'm out too. I have some left.
Take whatever you need.
Thanks.
Look, everyone's coming together.
It's because their princess is cute.
Oh, please. It is. Damn it!
House after house is like this!
How could this have happened?
How awful.
Say, Usad, what's that over there?
Let's take a look.
I'll improve my concentration.
Until I can bring out that power any time.
I can't consider myself stronger.
Wow, they're all such interesting books.
Is it really okay to take some with me?
Absolutely.
Take any you'd like.
I've read all of them.
Thanks so much.
And I'll definitely take
you up on that offer.
I've told you a hundred
times, there are no pirates.
Lying to us will only harm your country.
Harboring pirates is a major felony.
Hey, what's up?
Oh, welcome back.
I was surprised we were able to...
There's no evidence, and I
don't see any pirates here.
Do you?
Well, I...
I wonder if Luffy's woken up yet.
I doubt it.
Things would be noisier if he had.
Oh, man!
I slept good!
Hey, my hat!
Where the heck is my hat?
I'm starving, too!
Where's my breakfast? My
hat! My breakfast! My hat!
My breakfast!
My hat!
You just woke up, and you're
already making a racket.
And it won't be breakfast.
It'll be dinner.
It's evening.
Your hat's right over there, Luffy.
Lucky for you, a soldier found
it near the front of the palace.
I missed you.
I'm so relieved you
finally got well, Luffy.
Got well?
What do you mean?
I was never not well.
You dummy, you were in really
bad shape and had a high fever.
Vivi and Chopper have been
taking care of you all this time.
Really?
Thanks, you guys.
Oh, Luffy, you woke up.
Zoro, long time no see.
Wait a minute. How dare you?
You were out training, weren't you?
So what?
I didn't need your permission.
Of course you did!
I'm your doctor!
Where are your bandages?
It was too hard to move with them on.
You shouldn't be moving!
Long time no see.
Why'd I say that?
Probably because it has been long.
You've been asleep for three entire days.
Three days?
Three whole days? Uh-huh.
I missed 15 meals.
You sure calculate quickly
when it comes to food.
By his count, that's
like five meals a day.
I heard the captain's awake.
Dinner will be served shortly.
I hope you're all hungry.
What?
Hey, old tube-haired
guy, you're still alive?
So that cross-dressing
thing wasn't just an act.
No, everyone, you're mistaken.
This is Terracotta.
She's Igaram's wife and the
head of the palace's servers.
Thank you for helping Vivi and my husband.
I've heard of wives resembling their
husbands, but this is too weird.
I heard the captain eats a lot,
so I had my staff put together a little
snack to tide you and your friends over.
Thank you.
Greedy pig!
I'm gonna eat three whole
days worth of food, lady.
Oh, a challenge.
Good, I'm looking forward to it.
I've never lost to anyone's stomach,
so eat to your heart's content.
Geez, it seems to be Pucci less.
And with more manners too, I'm sure, this
is the Royal Dining Hall, not a trough.
Come on, Captain, keep
it up, I can handle it.
This smells good.
Loopy, you just snatched
my food, didn't ya?
You liar!
Hey, you keep eating like
that, you're gonna choke.
There's plenty more.
Snatch my food, will ya?
Some hot sauce will fix you.
That's very right, Loopy!
Eyelash, what did you get here?
What do you call that dish there?
It's called kanatha, noodles
baked in a brick oven.
Yummy!
Here's more. Eat up!
Oh, man, I never knew you were the king.
I guess that means you're
also Evie's dad, huh?
That's pretty cool.
Uh, maybe we should talk after dinner.
Yeah, okay.
And then another round down here, guys!
And water down here!
They're loud, uncouth, and disgusting.
I'll say, I can't watch.
The princess.
How could she keep laughing like that?
I want something!
I want
something!
This is the palace's royal bath.
Normally, we only use it
during the rainy season.
I'm royally impressed.
It's gorgeous.
I'm going in first.
Real mature, guys.
Well, that was some
dinner tonight, wasn't it?
I thought an after-dinner bath
would be a more sedative thing.
But it seems anything you lads get
involved with becomes a party very quickly.
Hey, Zoro! Look over here!
Look at what we're doing!
We're training!
Real funny.
Um, hey, where's the women's bath?
You're nuts!
And why would I tell you that?
That's where the princess is! I know.
It's right behind that wall.
Your majesty!
Hey, thanks, old guy.
You're the best!
This feels so good.
I wonder if a ship with a
big bath like this exists.
I'm sure one does.
The sea's full of surprises.
Think of what we've seen.
Giants and dinosaurs.
Blossoms blooming in a winter land.
If those things exist,
there must be plenty of more
amazing things out there in the sea.
I guess. My turn.
Thank you.
What are you all doing over there?
Keeping.
All right.
it'll cost 100,000 berries each
happiness
can't
make up your mind
what better think quick I was
thinking we might actually leave here
tonight really yeah we need to go
all the goings good we know that the
Marines are looking all over for us
and that means the ship is in danger.
Thank you.
Pervert.
Not for that!
For the country.
It's not that we don't appreciate it,
but is a king supposed to do that?
The swordsman is right, Your Majesty.
You're this land's sovereign ruler.
You should bow to no one.
Listen, Igaram.
Authority is something that
you wear over your clothes.
But we're in the bath now, and there is
no such thing as a naked king, is there?
I want to thank all of you
from the bottom of my heart,
as both a father and
a native of this land.
Alabasta will forever be
in your dead Straw Hats.
Thank you all very much.
I cannot tell you how
much we appreciate you.
Tonight? Yep.
We have to leave?
The Marines know we're here.
More will be coming.
I agree with Nami.
We need to get out now. Me too.
And not just because
she's got a pretty face.
Do you think we should leave, Luffy?
Yeah.
But only after we've had
some more yummy food.
No, now, you idiot egg.
What should we do, Igaram?
We have to let them know right away.
You're right, I agree.
Well, word of what's happened
here has traveled fast.
They've already released new Wanted
posters, and the bounties are quite large.
Roronoa Zoro, 60 million berries.
Monkey D.
Luffy, 100 million berries.
Incredible.
With bounties like that,
Marine Headquarters must have a keen
interest in capturing the Straw Hats.
You're no longer a mere pirate, Luffy.
Not since, you took down one of
the Seven Warlords of the Sea.